dellfinancialservices.com 2010-08-05

# Consumer Privacy Policies

**__** 

**_CONSUMER PRIVACY POLICY OF WEBBANK  
FOR DELL PREFERRED ACCOUNT_**

Thank you for utilizing the **Dell Preferred Account** offered by  **WebBank** (the Bank, or we, or us), with servicing by **Dell Financial Services L.L.C.** (DFS). One of our top priorities is to provide you, our customer, with outstanding products and services. In order to do this, we must collect, maintain and use certain personal and financial information about you and your activities with us. We recognize and respect your privacy concerns and expectations about how we use this information. We want you to know about our privacy policies and practices, and what we do to protect the information you share with us. 

This Consumer Privacy Policy applies to both current and former customers. Please read this Consumer Privacy Policy carefully and keep it for your records. 

**Collection and Use of Customer Information:** We collect, retain and use information about you to operate our business and to make products, services and other opportunities available to you. Much of the information we collect, such as account balances, credit information, and payment history, is of a non-public personal nature. We obtain this information (collectively, Customer Information) about you from a variety of sources. These include: (1) Information we receive from you on applications and other forms. This information may include but not be limited to your address, phone number, social security number, and employment (collectively, Personally Identifiable Information); (2) Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others. This may include information such as your account balances, payment history; and, (3) Information we receive from a consumer-reporting agency. This may include information about your credit history and creditworthiness. 

Also, when you visit any Website where the Dell Preferred Account is offered, we, DFS, and/or the Dell family of companies (Dell) may collect anonymous information to help us provide better customer service and to analyze trends and site statistics. For example, we may keep track of the domains from which people visit and we may also measure visitor activity on our Websites. We may combine this information with your Customer Information. 

All Customer Information we collect is made available to our servicer, DFS, to facilitate servicing your Dell Preferred Account. 

**Disclosure of Information:** We will not sell your Customer Information to any outside organizations without your consent. Additionally, we will not disclose your Customer Information to any of our related companies or outside organizations other than as described in this Policy. As described below, we may disclose Customer Information to (1) DFS; (2) Dell; (3) marketing service providers and financial institutions with which we may enter into joint marketing agreements from time to time; (4) companies that are related to us; (5) nonaffiliated third parties that offer financial and non-financial products and services; and, (6) other third parties, as permitted or required by law. 

**_To DFS:_** In order for DFS to properly service your Dell Preferred Account, we may provide your Customer Information to DFS. We also may share Customer Information with DFS for DFS’s own marketing purposes. You may tell us not to disclose your Customer Information to DFS for DFS’s own marketing purposes by following the Opt-Out Instructions in the box at the bottom of this policy. 

**_To Dell:_** In order for the Dell Preferred Account to function in a meaningful way for our customers and to allow Dell to provide offers to account holders, we may share certain Customer Information pertaining to our relationship with you with Dell. 

_**California Residents Only:**_ Customer Information shared with Dell is limited to your name and address, records of purchases you’ve made using your Dell Preferred Account and information concerning your Account, in connection with the offering or provision of Dell products and/or services. 

**_To Marketing Service Providers and Joint Marketing Partners:_** We may disclose Customer Information to companies that perform marketing services for us. We also may disclose all Customer Information (1) to companies that perform marketing services for one or more other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements, and (2) to other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements. 

_**California and Vermont Residents Only:**_ We do not disclose your Customer Information to (1) companies that perform marketing services for one or more other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements, or (2) other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements. 

**_To our Affiliates:_** To the extent we are permitted to do so by applicable law, we may share Customer Information with companies that are related to us by common ownership or control. 

**_California Residents Only:_** We only share your Customer Information with our affiliates in a manner that is permitted under the California Financial Information Privacy Act. If required by the Act, we will provide you with notice and the right to tell us not to make such disclosures prior to sharing your Customer Information with our affiliates. 

**_Vermont Residents Only:_** If you are a Vermont resident, we will not share your Customer Information with our affiliates without your express written consent. You do not need to take any action to limit this kind of information sharing. 

**_To Nonaffiliated Third Parties That Offer Financial and Non-Financial Products and/or Services:_** We may share Customer Information with companies that are not affiliated with us that offer products and/or services we think you’d be interested in. You may tell us not to disclose your Customer Information to them by following the Opt-Out Instructions in the box at the bottom of this policy. 

**_California and Vermont Residents Only:_** We do not share your Customer Information with nonaffiliated third parties for purposes of their offering products and services to you. You do not need to take any action to limit this kind of information sharing. 

**_To Other Third Parties:_** We may share your Customer Information with non-affiliated third parties that provide us with business and professional services in connection with your account, including but not limited to collections and invoicing and customer service. We may also share your Customer Information with non-affiliated third parties as otherwise permitted or required by law. 

**Protection of Information:** We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to protect the security and integrity of your Customer Information. 

**Changes to this Policy:**  Any changes we may make to our Consumer Privacy Policy will be posted on this page for a reasonable period of time before they become effective. If applicable law requires that any notice, including this Consumer Privacy Policy or any revisions to it, be delivered by an alternative method, we will deliver such notices in a manner that complies with such law. 

**Privacy Policy Effective Date: November 1, 2006**

**Opt-Out Instructions**

If you prefer that we not disclose your Customer Information to DFS (for its marketing purposes), Dell or non-affiliated third parties for their marketing purposes, call us at 1-866-351-9773 or write us at: P.O. Box 81575, Austin, TX 78708-1575. Please provide us with your name, address and account number. We cannot process your request without your account number. If your account is a joint account, any joint account holder may opt out on his/her own behalf and on behalf of other joint account holders.
